altitudedigital.com 2014-12-22

# Privacy Policy | Altitude Digital

## Privacy Policy

altitudedigital.com is committed to transparency and accountability in our privacy practices. The following statement describes altitudedigital.com’s Privacy Policy as it relates to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information altitudedigital.com receives from users of http://altitudedigital.com (this “Site”) and altitudedigital.com’s online video advertising platform services (the “Services”). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of the following:

### About altitudedigital.com and Consumers

Altitude Digital is not in the business of collecting, using, or selling consumer data; however it does offer tools and technologies to advertisers and publishers that allow them to collect and use user data. This is done primarily to enable these buyers and sellers of online video-advertising space to try and ensure that the audience they desire sees their ads and that the advertising itself is delivered and the performance of the advertising can be analyzed. Types of data that may be used for this purpose range from behavioral or interest-related information to geographical or demographical user data.

### Information Collected, and How It Is Collected

Personally-Identifiable Information. altitudedigital.com does not collect personally-identifiable information in order to help our clients buy, sell, and deliver online video advertising. “Personally-Identifiable Information” means information that alone or when in combination with other information that Altitude Digital.com collects may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate you. There may be some opportunities, for example when you use this Site, where you may choose to enter your name, contact information, and other personal details. For example, if you were interested in becoming one of our clients or using our Services you could provide us with contact details through our Site.

Where we collect personally-identifiable information you will have clear notification of what we are doing so that you can choose not to provide it.

Non-Personally-Identifiable Information. Non-personally-identifiable information is information that, without additional information, cannot be linked to a specific individual by altitudedigital.com. altitudedigital.com may collect non-personally-identifiable information while you are visiting our Site or the website of one of Altitude Digital.com’s advertisers or Web publishers (collectively, “altitudedigital.com Associates”). For example, while providing the Services to website publishers, advertisers and those working for them, Altitude Digital.com may collect your IP address, Web pages that you visit, the time and date, and whether or not you clicked on various advertisements (collectively, “Web Surfing Data”).

### Technologies We May Use for Data Collection.

altitudedigital.com and/or altitudedigital.com Associates use different types of technologies to collect non-personally-identifiable information, including cookies, action tags, Web beacons, and single pixel GIFs.  
Cookies. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes when you request through your browser to receive a particular Web page or content. altitudedigital.com uses cookies for three purposes.

  1. Persistent Cookies for altitudedigital.com Associates Use of Our Site. **** For our altitudedigital.com Associates who login to our Site so that they may use our Services, altitudedigital.com utilizes persistent cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Site. This functionality works as it does on many websites that work to enable you to have an easier experience logging in and navigating their websites. _We do not use persistent cookies in connection with helping altitudedigital.com Associates buy, sell, and deliver online video advertising._

  2. Session Cookies to Help Ad Delivery and Accounting. **** altitudedigital.com utilizes session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Services, to better understand how you interact with the Services, and to monitor aggregate usage by altitudedigital.com users and Web traffic routing on the Services. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser.

  3. User Data Cookies for Ad Targeting. altitudedigital.com utilizes cookies to store user data that can aid in targeting of advertisements. This data is usually collected by altitudedigital.com Associates and used to deliver advertisements that are more relevant to a user’s interests.

Use of Cookies By Others. Also, the Web publisher or advertiser may use cookies, action tags, GIFs, or Web beacons to collect information when you are visiting their websites. The information they collect is governed by their individual privacy policies, not altitudedigital.com’s. You are encouraged to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites that you visit. You can learn more about how cookies and related technologies are used in connection with online advertising and analytics by visiting: <http://www.aboutads.info/how-interest-based-ads-work>.

### Opt-Out Procedure and Cookie Control

If you do not want to receive any cookies from altitudedigital.com, you can disable cookies in your browser.

### Use of the Information We Collect

Use of Non-Personally-Identifiable Information. The non-personally-identifiable data that altitudedigital.com and/or altitudedigital.com Associates collect when using the Services are used for marketing and sales efforts and to better target advertisements to people across the different websites they visit. altitudedigital.com may also use the non-personally-identifiable data that it collects to better target content to individuals in an effort to create a personally relevant experience for each person. The non-personally identifiable data are also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals.

Use of Personally-Identifiable Information. altitudedigital.com uses personally-identifiable information it receives primarily to communicate with our altitudedigital.com Associates and Practices as we provide the Services. altitudedigital.com uses information we receive from business customer prospects in the same ways.

Data from altitudedigital.com Associates. altitudedigital.com allows altitudedigital.com Associates to import data that they have collected or purchased to deliver advertisements to certain audiences through the Services. altitudedigital.com is not responsible for and does not control the collection of this data. If you wish to opt out of collection of your information by third parties, then you must do so directly with those third parties.

### Sharing and Disclosure of Collected Information

altitudedigital.com does not provide personally-identifiable information to altitudedigital.com Associates or other third parties for their marketing purposes except under the following conditions. If a visitor to our Site provides personally-identifiable information as part of an inquiry about products or services provided by one of our altitudedigital.com Associates, we will provide that information only to that altitudedigital.com Associate so that they may attempt to respond to the inquiry. Like most businesses, we will use information we receive for our business purposes and keep this information for as long as we have a legitimate business purpose as permitted by applicable law.

Service Providers. altitudedigital.com may employ third-party companies and individuals to facilitate the Services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform website-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, Web analytics, and improvement of the Site’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Services are used. These third parties have access to your personal information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. altitudedigital.com may disclose information when necessary in cooperation with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or to law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including, but not limited to subpoenas), or to protect altitudedigital.com’s rights, property, or those of others.

Business Transfers. In addition to the above, there is also the possibility that altitudedigital.com may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company or otherwise be reorganized or sold. If that’s the case, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to your information.

### Security Precautions

altitudedigital.com makes efforts to maintain the security of its network and the data we collect. We use various technologies, including, in certain instances, encryption, to ensure security standards. altitudedigital.com treats data that is stored on its servers as confidential information. altitudedigital.com has an internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of customer and other data, limiting access only to those employees who we reasonably believe need to know such information for the purpose of performing their jobs. Please keep in mind, however, that the Internet is not a 100% secure medium. Therefore, although altitudedigital.com uses reasonable efforts to protect information, the possibility of somebody defeating its security measures does exist and none of our security measures should be viewed as a guarantee.

### International Visitors

altitudedigital.com is located in the United States of America, and the Site and Services are directed toward persons located within the United States of America. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, including those whose privacy laws may be more strict than U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States to altitudedigital.com. If you choose to use the altitudedigital.com Site and/or Services, you understand and consent to the processing of your personal information in the United States.

### Links to Web Publishers, Advertisers, and Other Websites

altitudedigital.com’s Services are combined with content from altitudedigital.com Associates and other third-party advertisers. altitudedigital.com’s Services may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit a Business Customer or other third-party advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third-party link, you will be directed to that third-party’s website. Our provision of a link to a website or a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement of that website or advertisement, nor is it an endorsement of the privacy or information security policies or practices of that website or advertiser. altitudedigital.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Web publishers, advertisers, or other websites that may be linked to altitudedigital.com’s Sites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, or solicit personal information from you. This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of information that we collect from you through our Services. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. You are encouraged to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

### Our Policy Toward Children

This Site is not directed to children under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally-identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally-identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact altitudedigital.com at “support@altitudedigital.com.” If altitudedigital.com becomes aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personally-identifiable information, altitudedigital.com will delete such information from our files.

**Accessing Your Personally-Identifiable Information, Making Changes, or Requesting Deletion**  
Where altitudedigital.com processes personally-identifiable information on our own behalf, you may request access to, correction of, or deletion of personal data held by us. If you desire to access such information we may hold, update the information, or for any privacy or data-protection-related question please write to: support@altitudedigital.com for assistance. Because we generally process data for others, for any of that data you should make your request directly to the party collecting the information or on whose behalf it has been collected.

### Contacting altitudedigital.com

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact altitudedigital.com by sending email to “support@altitudedigital.com” with “Privacy” in the subject line or you may write to:

Altitude Digital – dba: altitudedigital.com,

1037 Broadway

Suite B

Denver, CO 80203

### Acceptance of Privacy Statement

Your use of the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use Agreement, which can be found here. BY USING OUR SITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND IN OUR TERMS OF USE AGREEMENT.

### Changes to Privacy Policy

altitudedigital.com reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on the Site. Please check the effective date at the bottom of this page to determine if the Privacy Policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. In the event that any material changes are made to altitudedigital.com’s privacy practices, we will notify you by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and Services following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

### Effective Date

The Privacy Policy was last revised on August 1, 2013
